[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (1 + 2 \u00d7 5) \u00f7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "2",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "2",
        "1",
        "4"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 9 \u00d7 8) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "79",
      "options": [
        "78",
        "80",
        "81",
        "79"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 5 \u00d7 3) \u00f7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "8",
        "10",
        "7"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 8 \u00d7 3) \u00f7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "5",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "7",
        "6",
        "4"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 1 \u00d7 7) \u00f7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "2",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "1",
        "2",
        "4"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 9 \u00d7 5) \u00f7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "13",
      "options": [
        "12",
        "15",
        "13",
        "14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 3 \u00d7 10) \u00f7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "7",
      "options": [
        "7",
        "8",
        "9",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 9 \u00d7 3) \u00f7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "options": [
        "7",
        "10",
        "9",
        "8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (3 + 10 \u00d7 9) \u00f7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "46",
      "options": [
        "47",
        "45",
        "46",
        "48"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 1 \u00d7 3) \u00f7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "2",
        "1",
        "0"
      ]
    }
]